# **HASHIM EA**

### System Admin

+91 7204848365 / drhashimea@gmail.com Pathanamthitta Kerala 689501 India https://www.linkedin.com/in/drhashimea DOB: 28/05/1992

#### **PROFILE**

System Admin & Web Operation Manager specializing in web hosting and virtualization environments. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Good in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in billing and customer relations like WHMCS.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### System Admin - 2022 - Present

Zelev / Paris, France

Working as a system admin, Managing the Web and Systems environment for serving tutors and students mainly focussing on the education sector.

- Espocrm, Zabbix, Mattermost, Mailwizz, Uptimekuma, Mattermost, Nginx Proxy Manager, Nginx Load Balancer, HA Config for Wordpress
- Wordpress custom development, Staging, Plugin Integration, PHP, JS, Bootstrap,
- AWS SES Configuration, Cloudfront configuration
- Proxmox, (KVM, LXC), DNS
- Gitlab, Runner Setup for Automated Pipeline
- Team management

# System Admin - 2022 - Present

Kidyschool.com / Paris, France

Working as a system admin, Managing the Web and Systems environment for serving tutors and students mainly focussing on the education sector.

- Suitecrm, VtigerCrm, Wordpress Apache, Nginx, Setup & Maintenance
- Jitsi, Mattermost, Docker Setup
- PHP, JS Site Coding

# System Admin, Web Operation Manager, Sales - Sep 2012 - Jan 2022

Vpswindows.biz / Morocco

Executed & Managed Various Activities including Proxmox, Ceph Installation & Management

- TroubleShooting Client Problems
- Ticket Management, WHMCS Billing
- Gateway Integrations, WHMCS Modules Integrations.
- WebHosting, Cpanel, Plesk, Cyberpanel, aapanel experience
- Email Server, Domain Management, PowerDNS
- Proxmox, Ceph, Linux, Windows, VPS, Cloudinit Automations
- Sales, Marketing Experience

#### Startup Founder - 2019- Jan 2021

Careayu / India, Parttime

#### Infrastructure Development and Setup

- Wordpress, Woocommerce, Payment Gateway Integration,
- Openemr, Mailcow Email Server Setup & Customisation
- Azure, AWS Setup & Management, EC2 Deploy.
- Setup & Integrated Github workflow for App developments.
- Custom PHP Codes for Wordpress and Other Integrations
- Amazon EC2, SES (SMTP), Cloudfront, Setup

### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Ayurveda Medicine & Surgery - 2010 Sept - May 2015

Rajiv Gandhi University of Health Science Bangalore

• Graduate (4-1/2 years + 1 Year Internship)

#### Skills

- Webhosting Management & Experience with many panels
- Apache, Nginx Native hosting (Baremetal), Mysql
- PHP, Python, Js, HTML, CSS
- WHMCS Install, Management, Support, Sales, Admin, Root Level Experience
- Email Servers
- Proxmox
- Ceph, ZFS Setup & Management
- Linux debian, centos, ubuntu, mint &
  Windows, 2008, 2012, 2016, 2019, 2022 deployment & Troubleshoots
- Bash, command lines
- SSH, SFTP Connections, RDP
- Colocation Arrangements, PDU, Servers
- Wordpress, Woocommerce, Plugins
- Magento Setup
- Docker, Docker Compose Deployment
- Kubernetes (Entry Level)
- AWS, Azure
- Git Workflow
- Boting, Automation, Zeno, Selenium, UIPath etc
- MS Office, Google Sheets, Docs, Libreoffice
- Figma, Canva, Photoshop (Moderate)

#### **Interests**

- Blockchain, Cryptocurrency, VR, AR
- Travel
- Gaming
- Reading

#### **Personal Works**

- https://careayu.com
- https://liveayurvedalife.com